[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the mermaid-like creature from Brazilian folklore?", "correct_answer": "Iara", "incorrect_answers": ["Rusalka", "Aycayia", "Nereid"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This substance is a product of volcanic activity and is used as preservative in wine making.", "correct_answer": "sulfur dioxide", "incorrect_answers": ["hydrogen sulfide", "sulfurous acid", "sulfur trioxide"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What device was invented in the early 1910s by American race-car driver, Ray Harroun?", "correct_answer": "The rear view mirror", "incorrect_answers": ["The internal combustion engine", "The brake", "The tire iron"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Petite Danseuse de Quartorze Ans by Edgar Degas is a painting depicting a 14-year-old dancer.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "For whom was US pilot, Francis Gary Powers traded?", "correct_answer": "Rudolph Abel", "incorrect_answers": ["Paul Konerko", "David Ortiz", "Jackie Robinson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "pH, or the negative log of the H3O+ (hydronium ion) concentration, is the measure of acidity or basicity of an aqueous solution.  Which solution would have the lowest pH at room temperature?", "correct_answer": "a strong acid such as sulfuric acid", "incorrect_answers": ["a weak base such as ammonium hydroxide", "a weak acid such as acetic acid", "a strong base such as sodium hydroxide solution"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Robert Langdon, the main character in the movie The Da Vinci Code helps in the solving of a murder case by using his skills in what profession?", "correct_answer": "Symbologist", "incorrect_answers": ["Psychologist", "Detective", "Museum curator"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ray Walston, who plays Mr. Hand in Fast Times at Ridgemont High, was a regular cast member on which TV show?", "correct_answer": "My Favorite Martian", "incorrect_answers": ["My Three Sons", "The Rockford Files", "Lost In Space"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the first performer/band to have at least 36 Billboard Top Ten albums?", "correct_answer": "The Rolling Stones", "incorrect_answers": ["The Beatles", "Elvis Presley", "Frank Sinatra"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The husband of Catherine the Great was Peter I.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What planet is Chief Engineer Philo from in the Weird Al Yankovic movie UHF?", "correct_answer": "Zarcon", "incorrect_answers": ["Zirdon", "Zircon", "Zardon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What song is used as a de facto anthem of Sweden?", "correct_answer": "Thou Ancient, Thou Free", "incorrect_answers": ["Beautiful Sweden", "The Song of the King", "We Bow Before Thee"]}]